MAKSIM BAULIN

1435 Broadway, Burbank, CA, 91504, e-mail: baulim.maksim.1992@gmail.com, my web page: https://maksimbaulin.azurewebsites.net/, +1 (747) 244 8743

Summary

I am a web developer with over 3 years' experience in web application development. At the moment I am looking for an opportunity to develop computer games. I have excellent knowledge of C# and experience with the Unity 3D engine, including features, development of game mechanics, interface and visualization. I have experience in studying the community, managing projects and numerous processes. I am sure that my skills and experience will allow me to become an important player in your development team. I am willing to discuss my qualifications and experience at the interview.

Professional Experience

Full stack developer.NET C#

LTD Sports League, Russia (July 2021 – December 2022)

Development of new functionality, support for the existing functionality of the platform for additional education: schools, sports clubs, clubs, circles, courses, etc. Responsibilities: fixing front/back bugs, adding new functionality, testing functionality, optimizing, refactoring.

Full stack developer.NETC#

LTD BVB Tech, Russia (July 2019 – July 2021)

Non-commercial enterprise resource management system in the field of electric power industry (database of electric grid facilities, customer database, history of interaction with them, work scheduler). Responsibilities: fixing front/back bugs, adding new functionality, testing functionality, optimizing, refactoring.

Education

Bachelor Electric power industry, Power supply.

Kuzbass State Technical University, Kemerovo, Russia (Sep 2011 - July 2015)

Additional skills

C#, .NET, SQL, LINQ, HTML, CSS, MS SQL Server, Entity Framework, EF CORE, ASP.NET, ASP.NET CORE, REST API, Unity 2D, Unity 3D, Postman, Swagger, PostgreSQL, SQLite, Ajax, Javascript, Razor pages, Blazor components, Bootstrap, English intermediate, Polish intermediate, Russian native.